# Karol Moroz

Full Stack Software Developer @ Kaohsiung, TW

k.j.moroz@gmail.com

+886 916-945-080

■ Make Programming Fun Again

moroz

moroz.dev

## **Projects**

Print Your Own Foto @ https://artplate.store/pyof

September - October 2020 // Kobe Nutrition, PL

Web-based editor for crafting personalized photo collages, with support for Instagram-like filters, image frames, text overlay, cropping. Built with React.js talking to a Laravel back end, utilizing direct S3 uploads, CloudFront caching, CodePipeline.

#### Bazaro e-commerce

2020 // Side project

In my spare time, I co-operate with a friend—an certified Magento developer—to build a fast and reliable open source e-commerce platform in Elixir.

Horizon-Sim @ https://www.horizon-sim.com

2019 // Horizon, TW

Custom e-commerce solution built with Elixir, Phoenix, and React.js, with custom payment gateway integration.

### **Beacon Parameter Management System**

October - November 2018 // Access AP, TW

Full stack Single-Page Application built for a Japanese client, used to manage serial numbers of mass-produced devices, generate CSV reports and QR code sheets.

Donut MLOps @ https://donut.libgirl.com

March - May 2020 // Libgirl Co., Ltd., TW

A unified solution designed to keep track of ML models, efficiencies, evaluations, and iterations. Experimental one-click deployment of PyTorch models to GCP.

Injobs.pl @ https://www.injobs.pl

April - August 2017 // Injobs.pl Sp. z o. o., PL

Job board with company and applicant profiles, promoted job ads, and custom payment gateway integration. Built with Ruby on Rails.

BadBuyerList.org @ https://badbuyerlist.org/

December 2016 - January 2017 // GoodLife.TW 好生活, TW

Database for online sellers who have encountered problematic buyers and want to share their experiences with other sellers. Full rewrite of an earlier iteration of the application, built with Ruby on Rails.

## **Experience**

Software Developer @ Cogini Hong Kong Limited

May - December 2019 // Taipei, TW

Phoenix, React, Ruby on Rails, Python, Front End, CI/CD, Terraform, AWS

**Software Developer** @ Access AP Taiwan

October 2018 - May 2019 // Taipei, TW

Phoenix, React, in-house Elixir frameworks and libraries

Software Developer @ Reverse-Retail GmbH

September 2017 - July 2018 // Hamburg, DE

Ruby on Rails, MySQL

Software Development Intern @ Goodlife.TW

December 2016 - February 2017 // Taipei, TW

Ruby on Rails, MySQL

#### **Skills**

**Programming languages** 

Elixir, TypeScript, Ruby, Erlang, Python, HTML, CSS, C

**Libraries & Frameworks** 

Phoenix, React.js, Next.js, Gatsby, Vue.js, Ruby on Rails, Express, Apollo GraphQL, Flask, Sequelize, TypeORM, Mongoose

Cloud & DevOps

AWS: S3, CloudFront, CodePipeline, RDS, EC2, ACM, IAM Docker, Ansible, Terraform, Packer

**Tooling** 

Debian, macOS, Neovim, Spacemacs, VSCode, Webpack, PostgreSQL, MySQL/MariaDB, Adobe XD, Photoshop, Illustrator

### **Education**

## **National Taiwan Normal** University

2018 - // Taipei, TW

Master Programme, Graduate Institute of Translation and Interpretation

# **Adam Mickiewicz University**

2012 - 2016 // Poznań, PL

**Bachelor of Arts in Chinese Studies** 

# Languages

Native language

Polish

**Fluent** 

English (IELTS 8)

Mandarin Chinese (TOCFL 4) German (Goethe-Institut ZMP)

Good command

Russian, Spanish

Communicative

Japanese, Esperanto, Norwegian

#### **Interests**

Foreign languages, programming, traveling, ashtanga yoga, lifelong learning